<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WomenCare</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="map_screen">Map</string>
    <string name="chat_screen">ChatBot</string>
    <string name="profile">Library</string>
    <string name="welcome_screen_question">Signin or create an account</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">By continuing, you agree to our Terms of Service. We’ll
        handle your data according to our Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="feature_not_available">Feature not available</string>

    <string name="first_article_preview">  Do you know that a healthy diet can increase your fertility and prepare your body better for pregnancy? This means that your diet is not something you should be taking without proper considerations…</string>
    <string name="first_article"> What is a healthy diet?
            Do you know that a healthy diet can increase your fertility and prepare your body better for pregnancy? This means that your diet is not something you should be taking without proper considerations.
            A healthy diet, also a balanced diet, is a diet that involves the right proportions of all the seven classes of food needed for proper nourishment of your body.
          In case you cannot decide whether your diets are healthy or not, do not hesitate to contact your doctor. Together with him/her, you can draft out a nutritional weekly food timetable.

 What to eat and what to avoid eating
        There are so many diets around that have been proven medically to be healthy, and which can in turn benefits your body and health. Some of them include:
-Fruits — like, pineapples, watermelons, apples, berries, oranges, mango, and bananas
-Starchy foods— like potatoes, millet, yams, oatmeal, bulgur, and whole-wheat bread
-Proteins — like lean meats(minus liver), and chicken, eggs, seafood, beans and lentils
-Oils(in the right quantity) - like olive oil, vegetable oil, and oils in foods like seafood, avocado, and nuts
- Plenty of water

          So, what are the foods you should try your possible best to avoid?
-Fish that have small amounts of mercury,e.g, bluefin tuna, swordfish, shark, mackerel.
-Food and drinks that have caffeine are bad for you. Caffeine can be found in substances like tea, chocolate ,energy drinks, soda, etc. Your daily caffeine intake should not exceed 200 milligrams.
-Refrigerated pates, smoked seafood or meat spreads
        -Herbal products
- Alcohol ( in any amount)
-Unpasteurized juice, milk, soft cheeses, and so on.
</string>
    <string name="second_article_preview">Many a time a lot of women fidget about the body transformations that will occur during their pregnancy periods. Some even go as far as delaying getting pregnant because of this issue. While this kind of body transformations are inevitable and vary from women to women,you are not meant to be ashamed of them. By doing this, you will feel confident in yourself and have your self-esteem intact.
</string>
    <string name="second_article">  Many a time a lot of women fidget about the body transformations that will occur during their pregnancy periods. Some even go as far as delaying getting pregnant because of this issue. While this kind of body transformations are inevitable and vary from women to women,you are not meant to be ashamed of them. By doing this, you will feel confident in yourself and have your self-esteem intact.
            There are three stages of pregnancy every woman must pass through, namely: first trimester(conception to 12 weeks), second trimester(13 to 27 weeks),  third trimester (28 to 40 weeks). With each trimester comes a fairly distinct kind of transformation your body must go throughFirst trimester:In the first trimester, your baby\'s little body starts taking shape, and all those tiny organs begin to form. Meanwhile, your own body goes through some pretty big adjustments too. You might notice things like feeling queasy, super tired, and making more trips to the bathroom than usual. This stage is mostly filled with a lot of emotional and physical changes, which can be overwhelming (especially for the first timers). Furthermore, your hormones tend to be hyperactive during this stage, thereby contributing to these unpleasant pregnancy symptoms(such as frequent mood swings ) you will be experiencing.
          A supportive bra will also be needed due to the enlargement of your mammary glands, causing your breasts to swell in preparation for successful breastfeeding process. In addition, the veins on your breasts become more noticeable. Also, you need to consider wearing bigger clothes to prevent tightening your body.
</string>


    <string name="third_article">   Based on the research conducted by American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG), between 14-23% of women will struggle with some symptoms of depression during pregnancy. Depression is a frequent health condition that brings about repeated feelings of gloominess and changes in how you think, eat and act. It is something that should not be taken with levity hands, as it can both be dangerous to you and your baby\'s health.
           Depression can take in any forms like bipolar II disorder, postpartum depression, and so on. So, you should be sensitive enough to your mood to detect any form of depression symptoms - sleep disturbances, suicidal thoughts, self-hatred, restlessness, irritability, anger outbursts, et cetera.Causes of Depression.What are the factors that can make you susceptible to depression? There are countless reasons that can lead you into depression or dejection. These reasons are a mix of social, psychological, economical and biological factors, some of which are highlighted below:-Loss of loved ones like husbands, family members, friends. -Physical or verbal abuse can contribute to depression.-Certain drugs like isotretinoin and corticosteroids can increase your risk of getting depressed.-Unpleasant life events like money worries, divorce, illness, miscarriage.
</string>

    <string name="third_article_preview">Based on the research conducted by American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG), between 14-23% of women will struggle with some symptoms of depression during pregnancy. Depression is a frequent health condition that brings about repeated feelings...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>



    <string name="app_tagline">Better surveys with Jetpack Compose</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="sign_in_guest">Sign in as guest</string>
    <string name="sign_in_create_account">Sign in or create an account</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="user_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create account</string>


    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="show_password">Show password</string>
    <string name="hide_password">Hide password</string>

    <!-- survey-->
    <string name="question_count">\u00A0of %d</string>
    <string name="select_one">Select one.</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select all that apply.</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select date.</string>

    <!-- question 1-->
    <string name="in_my_free_time">In my free time I like to …</string>
    <string name="read">Read</string>
    <string name="work_out">Work out</string>
    <string name="draw">Draw</string>
    <string name="play_games">Play video games</string>
    <string name="dance">Dance</string>
    <string name="watch_movies">Watch movies</string>

    <!-- question 2 -->
    <string name="pick_superhero">Pick a Compose comic character</string>
    <string name="spark">Spark</string>
    <string name="lenz">Lenz</string>
    <string name="bugchaos">Bug of Chaos</string>
    <string name="frag">Frag</string>


    <!-- question 1-->
    <string name="how_would_you_describe_your_overall_health">How would you describe your overall health?</string>
    <string name="excellent">Excellent</string>
    <string name="good">Good </string>
    <string name="fair">Fair</string>
    <string name="poor">Poor</string>
    <string name="i_do_not_know">I do not know</string>-->

    <!-- question 2 -->
    <string name="do_you_have_excessive_severe_pain_or_excessive_bleeding_during_your_periods">Do you experience severe pain or excessive bleeding during your periods?</string>
    <string name="always">Always</string>
    <string name="often">Often</string>
    <string name="sometimes">Sometimes</string>
    <string name="never">Never</string>

    <!-- question 3  -->
    <string name="takeaway">When was the last time you ordered takeaway because you couldn\'t be bothered to cook?</string>

    <!-- question 4-->
    <string name="selfies">How do you feel about selfies 🤳?</string>
    <string name="how_old_are_you">How old are you?</string>
    <string name="are_you_aware_of_the_risks_associated_with_pregnancy_and_childbirth">Are you aware of the risks associated with pregnancy and childbirth?</string>

    <!-- question 5-->
    <string name="selfie_skills">Show off your selfie skills!</string>
    <string name="add_photo">ADD PHOTO</string>
    <string name="retake_photo">RETAKE PHOTO</string>

    <string name="survey_result_title">Compose</string>
    <string name="survey_result_subtitle">Congratulations, you are Compose</string>
    <string name="survey_result_description">You are a curious developer, always willing to try
        something new. You want to stay up to date with the trends to Compose is your middle name.</string>
    <string name="strongly_dislike">Strongly\nDislike</string>
    <string name="strongly_like">Strongly\nLike</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="hundred">100</string>
    <string name="Ten">10</string>
    <string name="fifty">50</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="somewhat">SomeWhat</string>









    <string name="action_go">Go</string>
    <string name="action_try">Try it</string>

    <!-- Menu strings -->
    <string name="menu_summarize_title">Generate text from text-only input</string>
    <string name="menu_summarize_description">Sample app that summarizes text</string>
    <string name="menu_reason_title">Generate text from text-and-image input (multimodal)</string>
    <string name="menu_reason_description">Sample app for uploading images and asking about them</string>
    <string name="menu_chat_title">Build multi-turn conversations (chat)</string>
    <string name="menu_chat_description">Sample app demonstrating a conversational UI</string>

    <!-- Summarize sample strings -->
    <string name="summarize_label">Text</string>
    <string name="summarize_hint">Enter text to summarize</string>

    <!-- Photo Reasoning sample strings -->
    <string name="reason_label">Question</string>
    <string name="reason_hint">Upload an image and then ask a question</string>
    <string name="add_image">Add Image</string>

    <!-- Chat sample strings -->
    <string name="chat_label">Message</string>
    <string name="action_send">Send</string>


</resources>